{"data":[{"question":"The continental shelves is the shallow area of the ocean floor that is closest to the continents.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Fishing","b":"to contain","c":"that","d":"levels","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Fishing-> fishes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The average adult get two to five colds each year.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"ability","b":"contributed greatly","c":"him","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Him-> his","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Fishing have been found to contain a particular type of fat that may help lower blood cholesterol levels.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Industrial","b":"most often","c":"for","d":"measure","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Measure-> measuring","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Benjamin Franklin's ability to learn from observation and experience contributed greatly to him success in public life.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"probably","b":"for her novel","c":"publishing","d":"in 1982","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Publishing-> published","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Industrial lasers are most often used for cutting, welding, drilling, and measure.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has studied","b":"effects","c":"color","d":"on people's","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Has studied-> have studied","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Alice Walker is probably best known for her novel The Color Purple, publishing in 1982.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the","b":"philosophy","c":"was elected","d":"which was","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Philosophy-> philosopher","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Psychologists at the University of Kansas has studied the effects of the color of a room on people's behavior.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Certain","b":"likely","c":"an allergic","d":"another","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Another-> other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Certain pollens are more likely to cause an allergic reaction than another.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have","b":"access","c":"instantly available","d":"by push","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- By push-> by pushing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Computers have made access to information instantly available just by push a few buttons.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Mined","b":"ago","c":"the","d":"know","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Know-> known","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Mined over 2,000 years ago, copper is one of the earliest know metals.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Many","b":"expresses","c":"barrenness","d":"isolation","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Many-> none","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}